<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Katherine Chandler on Home</title>
    <link>http://katherinechandler.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Katherine Chandler on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:48:17 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://katherinechandler.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Themes in Anthony Bourdain&#39;s &#39;Parts Unknown&#39;</title>
      <link>http://katherinechandler.io/post/bourdain_nlp_clustering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:48:17 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katherinechandler.io/post/bourdain_nlp_clustering/</guid>
      <description>Like many travelers I was saddened by the death of travel personality Anthony Bourdain. An ongoing (and ridiculous) theme that I espouse is insinuating that Bourdain &amp;lsquo;stole&amp;rsquo; my travel destinations. &amp;ldquo;Pfffff, he WOULD go to Armenia,&amp;rdquo; I complain. But in reality, I greatly valued the always interesting and wonderfully humanistic viewpoint that Bourdain presented while exploring the world&amp;rsquo;s complex places. I&amp;rsquo;ll miss this viewpoint terribly, and in this project I applied NLP and clustering tools to identify overarching themes in Bourdain&amp;rsquo;s CNN series Parts Unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Classifying Household Income from US Census Data</title>
      <link>http://katherinechandler.io/post/kaggle-census-boosted-classifiers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katherinechandler.io/post/kaggle-census-boosted-classifiers/</guid>
      <description>With this project I dug into classification algorithms and selected a data set from the &amp;lsquo;Adult Census Income&amp;rsquo; Kaggle Challenge. The data supplied for this challenge data was extracted from the 1994 census and contains aggregated demographic information (associated with a class &amp;lsquo;weight&amp;rsquo;) for US households. The prediction task is a binary classification to determine if a given household&amp;rsquo;s annual income is above $50,000 a year.
In this blog I present a high-level overview of my analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Salt Lake City&#39;s Real Estate Market</title>
      <link>http://katherinechandler.io/post/salt-lake-city-zillow-stat-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katherinechandler.io/post/salt-lake-city-zillow-stat-approach/</guid>
      <description>In the previous project I explored the &amp;lsquo;bigger is not better&amp;rsquo; movement with an initial exploratory analysis of active and historic real estate data in the Salt Lake City metro area. I found that small homes in the urban center are more valuable per square foot than large suburban homes and maintain their value more robustly during times of market contraction. In this project, I used statistical inference and linear regression to validate these initial findings and explore the ways in which various factors impact home pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living small in the city or large in the &#39;burbs?</title>
      <link>http://katherinechandler.io/post/salt-lake-city-zillow-eda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katherinechandler.io/post/salt-lake-city-zillow-eda/</guid>
      <description>I am a proponent of smaller homes, and recent dinner discussions have made me curious about the relationship between the size of a home and its relative appreciation in value. My vocal family members maintain that &amp;lsquo;You&amp;rsquo;re better off owning a tiny home downtown than a mansion in the &amp;lsquo;burbs!!!&amp;rsquo;. Indeed, current hipster cannon asserts that bigger is not better when it comes to housing. While there are many non-economic merits of a modestly sized home, I was curious about how the &amp;lsquo;small-home&amp;rsquo; movement holds up to economic reality.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>