<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Blog on Home</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Blog on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Salt Lake City&#39;s Real Estate Market</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/zillow_stats_post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/zillow_stats_post2/</guid>
      <description>In the previous project I explored the &amp;lsquo;bigger is not better&amp;rsquo; movement with an initial exploratory analysis of active and historic real estate data in the Salt Lake City metro area. I found that small homes in the urban center are more valuable per square foot than large suburban homes and maintain their value more robustly during times of market contraction. In this project, I used statistical inference and linear regression to validate these initial findings and explore the ways in which various factors impact home pricing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Living small in the city or large in the &#39;burbs?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/zillow_eda_post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/zillow_eda_post1/</guid>
      <description>I am a proponent of smaller homes, and recent dinner discussions have made me curious about the relationship between the size of a home and its relative appreciation in value. My vocal family members maintain that &amp;lsquo;You&amp;rsquo;re better off owning a tiny home downtown than a mansion in the &amp;lsquo;burbs!!!&amp;rsquo;. Indeed, current hipster cannon asserts that bigger is not better when it comes to housing. While there are many non-economic merits of a modestly sized home, I was curious about how the &amp;lsquo;small-home&amp;rsquo; movement holds up to economic reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>